[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "Яблоко",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "Banana",
        "back": "Банан",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "pear",
        "back": "Груша",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "cucumber",
        "back": "огурец",
        "setName":"css-свойство"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "apple",
        "back": "Яблоко",
        "setName":"css-свойство"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "tomato",
        "back": "Помидор",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "carrot",
        "back": "Морковь",
        "setName":"css-свойство"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "beet",
        "back": "Свекла",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "potato",
        "back": "Картошка",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "parsley",
        "back": "Петрушка",
        "setName":"css-свойство"
    }
]